Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Architectural projects, unnumbered
  - Riverview Cemetery Chapel, Portland, OR [Religious], 1939
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 5 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - Rohm and Haas Building, Philadelphia, PA
    - Miscellaneous (Box 469)
  - Roman Catholic Cathedral [Religious]
    - Drawings (Tube 461)
  - Roosevelt Memorial Statue Pedestal [Monument]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
  - Rosaria Stage [Other]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
  - Roseburg Library, Roseburg, OR [Library]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 16)
  - St. Francis Hospital, HTB Inc. Architects, Tulsa, OK [Hospital], 1987
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: Miscellaneous consulting: St. Francis Hospital, Tulsa OK.
    - Drawings (Tube 500)
  - St. Joseph's Catholic Church, Roseburg, OR [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 469)
  - St. Margaret of Cortona Church, Columbus, OH [Religious], 1966-1967
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: St. Margaret of Cortona Catholic Church, Columbus OH.
    - Drawings (Tube 790)
    - Drawings (Tube 879)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 469)
  - St. Mary's Catholic Cathedral, San Francisco, CA [Religious]
    - Drawings, sketched by Belluschi (Box 470)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 469)
    - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 470)
  - St. Matthews Church [Religious]
    - Drawings (Tube 490)
  - Sanford Insurance Co. [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
  - Sawtell House, East Moreland, Portland, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 294)
  - R. W. Schmeer, OR [Other]
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - School Building, Tillamook, OR [Educational]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Schoolhouse, Wheeler, OR [Educational]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Seattle First National Bank, Seattle, WA [Commercial], 1966
    - Drawings (Tube 812)
  - Seattle National Bank, Seattle, WA [Commercial]
    - Drawings, tracings from the office of Doyle and Merriam (Tube 527)
  - Seattle Public Library, Seattle, WA [Library]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 470)
  - Security Savings & Trust [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - F. M. Seller Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 3)
  - Selling-Hirsch Property [Other], 1928
    - Drawings (Tube 303)
  - Sellwood Christian Science Church (proposed), Portland, OR [Religious], 1941
    - Drawings (Tube 461)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 3 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - Servel Inc. Appliances, Evansville, IN [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 2)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
    - Drawings, refrigerators (Drawer MCD 22)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 24)
  - Shellmar Products [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Sherman Clay Warehouse [Industrial]
    - Drawings, stairway (Drawer SD 4)
  - Sherwood Nursery, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
  - Simonds Manufacturing Co. Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
  - L. J. Simpson Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings, house and shore acres (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Sinclair Provision Co. [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Skidmore residence (folder title: "House for Mr. and Mrs. Louis Skidmore"), Winter Haven, FL [Residential]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 463)
  - Smith College Dorm, Skidmore Owings & Merrill [Residential], Photographs
    - Photographs (Box 534)
  - Smith Warehouse Alterations [Industrial], 1935
    - Drawings (Tube 462)
  - South Cove Project, Boston, MA [Other], 1974
    - Drawings, public works standards (Tube 740)
    - Drawings, site preparation (Tube 809)
  - South St. Station, Sert Jackson Assoc., Boston, MA [Other], 1969
    - Drawings (Tube 909)
  - S. P. & S. Ry [Realty?] Co. Warehouse [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - Speed-Grits [Commercial]
    - Drawings, sander assembly (Drawer MCD 18)
  - A. C. Spencer Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Standard Oil Co. [Commercial]
    - Drawings, observation tower (Drawer SD 2)
    - Drawings, Yeon Building (Drawer SD 2)
  - State Office Building (proposed), Salem, OR [Government], 1936
    - Drawings (Tube 303)
  - State Parking Garage, Portland, OR [Government], 1967
    - Drawings (Tube 805)
  - Statesman Printing Co. [could be Oregon Statesman or Idaho Statesman]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - STD. 56 Store Building [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 3)
  - Stearns Building Alterations
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Stevens Building, Oregon Mutual Life Insurance Co. Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Stevens Building, Widman-Lewis, 1913
    - Drawings (Tube 309)
  - R. J. Stewart Machine Shop [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 16)
  - Stimson Center, John Graham and Co., Seattle, WA [Commercial], 1985
    - Drawings (Tube 499)
  - Stores, Ainsworth, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1934
    - Drawings, block of one-story stores (Tube 457)
  - R. H. Strong
    - Drawings, cottage (Drawer MCD 25)
    - Drawings, house in Portland Heights (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Strong-McNaughton Project [Commercial], 1929
    - Drawings (Tube 308)
  - Sun Life Insurance Company Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings
  - Sunset Mountain Park development, Los Angeles, CA [Other]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Super Hotel (proposed), Portland, OR [Residential], 1927
    - Drawings (Tube 543)
  - Technology Square, Kendall Square, Cambridge, MA [Urban Planning], 1960-1970
    - Drawings (Tube 791)
    - Drawings (Tube 761)
    - Drawings (Tube 762)
    - Miscellaneous, 565 Technology Square (Box 463)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Temple Adath Israel, Merion, PA [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Temple Brith Kodesh, Rochester, NY [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Temple Israel, Swampscott, MA [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Theater and Office Building [Other]
    - Drawings, sketch (Drawer MCD 7)
  - Theaters, miscellaneous [Other]
    - Drawings, sketches (Drawer MCD 7)
  - Leo F. Thibau Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings, house sketches (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Third Harbor Crossing, Boston Trans Planning Review, Boston, MA [Other], 1972
    - Drawings (Tube 734)
    - Drawings (Tube 807)
  - W. L. Thompson [Other], 1925
    - Drawings, sketches; 3 items (Tube 308)
  - Timberline Hotel, Mt. Hood, OR [Residential], 1934
    - Drawings (Tube 542)
    - Specifications (Box 471)
  - Tobin School, Cambridge, MA [Educational]
    - Drawings (Tube 790)
  - Tremont St. Subway, Welton Beckett & Beacon Consultants, Boston, MA [Other], 1961
    - Drawings, reference (Tube 918)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - Trinity Church (folder title: "Proposed chapel for Trinity Church"), Boston, MA [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 469)
  - Trinity Church, Concord, MA [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - Troy High School Building [Educational]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 1)
    - Drawings, noted as "FJS Highschool" (Drawer MCD 5)
  - Turner Residence, South Lincoln, MA [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 803)
  - Two Charles Center, Pratt St., Baltimore, MD [Urban Planning], 1965-1971; includes landscaping, Hilton Hotel, parking garage
    - Drawings (Tube 793)
  - Union Block Alterations
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
  - Union Pacific Building (proposed), Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, job title given as "Union Pacific System"; 5 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - Union Station, Portland, OR [Other], 1929
    - Drawings (Tube 599)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 2 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
  - United Airlines Office Building and Hangar, Kahn Architects, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1939
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
  - U. S. Bancorp Headquarters Office Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1982
    - Drawings (Tube 517)
  - U. S. Bank, Portland, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings, 1928; proposed Eastside branch (Tube 464)
    - Drawings, proposed Oak St. addition (Tube 464)
    - Drawings, 1929; Financial Center Building (Tube 464)
    - Drawings, main branch (Tube 464)
    - Photographs (Box 534)
  - U. S. Bank, Eugene Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings, 1941 (Tube 464)
  - U. S. Department of Labor Employment Office [Government]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 16)
  - U. S. Embassy residence, Paris [Residential]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - U. S. National Bank [no location given]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - U. S. National Bank, Medford, OR
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 4 items (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - U. S. Navy Post-Graduate School, Monterey, CA [Educational]
    - Photographs (Box 534)
  - Universal Auto Co. Garage [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Universita degli studi di Ancona, Progetto de Massima, Ancona, Italy [Educational]
    - Drawings, blank architectural mylar (Tube 895)
  - University of Louisville, Louisville, KY [Educational]
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: University of Louisville.
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - University of Massachusetts, see Boston campus, University of Massachusetts
  - University of Notre Dame, Institute for Advanced Religious Studies, Notre Dame, IN [Educational]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - University of Oklahoma City, see Chapel, University of Oklahoma City
  - University of Rhode Island housing complex, Kingston, RI [Educational]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - University of Texas at Austin Performing Arts Center, Austin, TX [Educational], 1974
    - Drawings (Tube 808)
  - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA [Educational], 1963-1967
    - Drawings, 1965-1967; Architecture Library, Fine Arts Center, Drama elevations (Tube 781)
    - Drawings, 1965; Architecture Library, Fine Arts Center (Tube 754)
    - Drawings, 1967; Architecture Library, Fine Arts Center, final scheme (Tube 736)
    - Drawings, 1967; Architecture Library, Fine Arts Center, final scheme (Tube 737)
    - Drawings, 1967; School of Architecture and library building, drawings and plans (Tube 877)
    - Drawings, 1967; School of Architecture and library building, drawings and plans (Tube 878)
    - Drawings, 1970; drama education building, mechanicals (Tube 755)
    - Drawings, 1970; Fine Arts Center, phase 2 (Tube 741)
    - Drawings, 1970; Fine Arts Center, phase 2 (Tube 742)
    - Drawings, 1963-1965; Fine Arts Center, business school addition (Tube 907)
    - Miscellaneous, Fine Arts Center (Box 472)
  - Upson Co. [Commercial]
    - Drawings, design of executive offices (Drawer MCD 5)
  - Valley & Siletz Railway Roundhouse [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
  - Vancouver Housing Authority
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - E. A. Van Sicklin Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Virginia Hill Hotel [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
  - Volunteer [possibly Volunteers in Service to America, aka VISTA] Home for Girls [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
  - Volunteers of America [possibly Volunteers in Service to America, aka VISTA] Children's Home [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
  - Wall Estate
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - War Emergency Housing [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 16)
  - War Memorial Building, Gymnasium and Swimming Pool, Cambridge, MA [Monument]
    - Drawings (Tube 838)
  - Warehouse for Galvinizing/Galvinizers, Portland, OR [Industrial], 1945
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 457)
  - Warehouse, 18th and Sandy
    - Drawings, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - Warren [Other]
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - Washburne Department Store Alterations (proposed), Portland, OR [Commercial], 1937
    - Drawings (Tube 462)
  - Washburne's Store, Eugene, OR
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - Washington Bridge, Providence, RI [Other]
    - Miscellaneous, Fine Arts Center (Box 472)
  - Washington State Convention and Trade Center, Seattle, WA [Other], [1983]
    - Drawings (Tube 505)
    - Drawings (Tube 506)
    - Drawings (Tube 507)
  - Waste Water Treament Plant, Auburn-Lewiston, ME [Industrial], 1969
    - Drawings (Tube 730)
  - Water Storage Tank, Portland, OR [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Wellesley Office Park, Life Center Housing, Wellesly, MA [Commercial], 1965
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: Wellesley Office Park.
    - Drawings (Tube 797)
    - Drawings (Tube 802)
  - Wells Fargo Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1906
    - Drawings (Tube 308)
  - West Made Desk Co. [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
  - West Shore Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1939
    - Drawings (Tube 462)
  - West Union Baptist Church [Religious]
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - Westminster Church, Chehalis, WA [Religious]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
  - Westmoreland
    - Drawings, entrance gate (Drawer MCD 7)
  - White Residence, Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Whitfield Residence, Alterations
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - Wilkes Apartment House [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Willamette University, Salem, OR [Educational], 1937-1941
    - Drawings, 1941; inscription for Collins Hall (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, 1937; Kimball Hall alterations (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, miscellaneous data and campus layouts (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, chapel, proposed (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, 1937; library, proposed (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, 1939; student union building, proposed (Tube 310)
    - Drawings, Weller Hall new entrance to stairway, etc. (Tube 310)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 8 items (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - A. B. Winfree Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 2)
  - Worcester Center, Worcester, MA [Commercial], 1968-1972
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 731)
    - Drawings, 1969 (Tube 922)
    - Drawings, 1970-1971 (Tube 898)
    - Drawings, 1970-1972; reference (Tube 899)
  - Worker hotel, 125 rooms [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - World Trade Center, Baltimore, MD [Commercial], 1969
    - Drawings (Tube 792)
  - Wren Tea House [Other]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 7)
  - Yakima Valley Bank [Commercial]
    - Drawings, tracings from the office of Doyle and Merriam (Tube 527)
  - J. B. Yeon Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
  - YWCA building, Pittsburgh, PA [Institutional]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 472)
  - Unidentified
    - Building, 146-1/2 1st St., Alterations, drawings (Drawer SD 5)
    - Building, 5th and Oak, Alterations, drawings (Drawer SD 7)
    - Building, 7th and East Pine, drawings (Drawer SD 7)
    - Hotel, floor plans (Tube 482)
    - Office building, 1927; renderings and hardback sketches; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Office building, main elevator, 1936; renderings and hardback sketches; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Parking facilities "Apt. Dev. Fork. Oliver", renderings and hardback sketches; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Public building complex, renderings (Tube 482)
    - Shopping center, renderings and hardback sketches; 4 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Show windows for electric store, Alder St., drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Miscellaneous
    - A. E. Doyle, miscellaneous drawings and sketches (Drawer SD 2)
    - Automotive Camping, drawings; 2 items (Tube 307)
    - bp [building permits?], drawings; 2 items (Tube 482)
    - Broomfield Ave, NY, drawings (Drawer MCD 5)
    - Building Permits Chart, 1900-1944, drawings (Tube 307)
    - Buildings, miscellaneous, at 5th and Yamhill, drawings (Drawer SD 3)
    - City of Portland - Base map, 1965; drawings (Tube 919)
    - Doyle & Patterson, Architects, miscellaneous drawings and sketches (Drawer SD 2)
    - Elevator cars for building, drawings; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Grates, drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
    - Hardware, lamps, etc., drawings (Drawer MCD 18)
    - Mantelpieces, drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
    - Mantelpieces, drawings (Drawer MCD 18)
    - Map, topographic, inner harbor with overlays and aerial views (Tube 889)
    - Map, topographic, Medfield and Norwood (Tube 909)
    - Maps, miscellaneous, drawings (Tube 307)
    - Maps, zoning - Washington & Oregon, drawings (Tube 307)
    - Weather beacon, photographs; 20 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Weathervanes and fireplace fenders, drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
    - Whidden and Lewis, specifications; 3 folders (Box 230)
    - Windmill tower, photographs; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous drawings (Drawer SD 6)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Commercial] (Box 534)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Commercial], businesses; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Educational], floor plan for gym (Box 534)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Religious], churches; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Religious] (Box 534)
    - Miscellaneous photographs [Residential], houses; 2 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, includes photos with "George B. Campbell" written on back, negatives; 2 folders (Box 534)
    - Miscellaneous photographs (Oversize 5)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, scrapbook, multiple numbered and unnumbered projects (Oversize 5)
    - Miscellaneous photographs, 11 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous renderings and hardback sketches, churches; 3 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
    - Miscellaneous renderings and hardback sketches, houses; 6 items (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Miscellaneous renderings and hardback sketches, public buildings; 30 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous renderings and hardback sketches, schools and colleges; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Miscellaneous renderings and hardback sketches, 6 items (Drawer 9 / 5)
- Job specifications
  - Job specifications regarding numbered and/or named architectural projects. The itemized listing for this material is incorporated into the two "Architectural projects" series series above, under the appropriate project. (Box 1-3)
  - Specifications, for numbered and/or named architectural projects. The itemized listing for this material is incorporated into the two "Architectural projects" series series above, under the appropriate project. (Box 230-255)
  - Specifications, for numbered and/or named architectural projects. The itemized listing for this material is incorporated into the two "Architectural projects" series series above, under the appropriate project. (Box 441-453)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 455)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 456)
- Correspondence
  Correspondence remains largely as organized by Belluschi. For this reason, there are multiple chronological and alphabetical sequences. Researchers are advised to skim the entire series to ensure locating all relevant material.
  Correspondence pertaining to specific numbered or unnumbered projects is itemized in the first two series above, "Architectural projects, numbered" and "Architectural projects, unnumbered."
  - Correspondence, architectural projects
    - Correspondence regarding numbered and/or named architectural projects. The itemized listing for this material is incorporated into the two "Architectural projects" series series above, under the appropriate project. (Box 4-191)
  - Correspondence, chronological (I)
    - [General], 1924-1926 (Box 192)
    - [General], 1926-1929 (Box 193)
    - [General], 1930-1931 (Box 194)
    - [General], 1932-1940 (Box 195)
  - Correspondence, alphabetical (I)
    - American Institute of Architects (Box 196)
    - Community Chest (Box 196)
    - Commonwealth, Inc. (Box 196)
    - Contractors' qualifications (Box 196)
    - Cooper, Miles Kaye (Box 196)
    - Crowell, W. H. (Box 196)
    - D (Box 196)
    - Draftsmen and engineers (Box 197)
    - E (Box 197)
    - Elmendoorf Hospital, Alaska (Box 197)
    - Executives Association (Box 197)
    - F, G (Box 197)
    - Greene, C. K., 1927 (Box 197)
    - H, I, J (Box 197)
    - K (Box 198)
    - Kroeker, J. Donald (Box 198)
    - L, M (Box 198)
    - Medford Shopping Center, 2 folders (Box 198)
    - Miscellaneous bids (Box 198)
    - Miscellaneous jobs (Box 198)
    - Miscellaneous jobs and clippings, 1936-1942 (Box 198)
    - N, O (Box 199)
    - Okinawa project, 2 folders (Box 199)
    - Oregon Mutual Life (Box 199)
    - Oswego Country Club, 2 folders (Box 200)
    - P (Box 200)
    - Petro Belluschi, personal (Box 200)
    - prospective jobs, 1928-1942; 9 folders (Box 201)
    - Recommendation letters (Box 202)
    - Reed College (Box 202)
    - Q, R (Box 202)
    - Reports and appraisals (Box 202)
    - S (Box 202)
    - Sample contracts (Box 203)
    - Santa Fe Railway (Box 203)
    - Social Security, A. E. Doyle and Associates (Box 203)
    - State Unemployment Compensation Commission, Doyle, 2 folders (Box 203)
    - T (Box 203)
    - Tacoma Post Office Competition (Box 203)
    - Transportation and mail schedule (Box 203)
    - U, V (Box 203)
    - Unit prices (Box 203)
    - W (Box 203)
    - Whitefield and Stratford (Box 203)
    - X, Y, Z (Box 203)
  - Correspondence, alphabetical (II)
    - A (Box 204)
    - Aloi, Roberto (Box 204)
    - Aluminum Company of Canada (Box 204)
    - America-Italy Society (Box 204)
    - American Home (Box 204)
    - American Institute of Architects, 2 folders (Box 204)
    - American Institute of Architects, 2 folders (Box 205)
    - American Society of Architects and Planners (Box 205)
    - Applications (Box 205)
    - Application letters, 5 folders (Box 206)
    - Architects (Box 207)
    - Architectural Advisory Commission (Box 207)
    - Architectural Forum (Box 207)
    - Architectural Record (Box 207)
    - Arts and Architecture (Box 207)
    - Australian exhibit (Box 207)
    - B (Box 207)
    - Bank data and letters (Box 207)
    - Bank statements and deposit slips (Box 208)
    - Belluschi gift fund (Box 208)
    - Belluschi, personal, 2 folders (Box 208)
    - Belluschi, Skidmore, Owings & Merrill (Box 208)
    - Belluschi speeches and dittos (Box 208)
    - Belluschi, trips east (Box 208)
    - Better Homes and Gardens (Box 208)
    - Blue Cross plan (Box 209)
    - Brown, Elliott (Box 209)
    - City Club of Portland, 2 folders (Box 209)
    - Commendation letters (Box 209)
    - Commonwealth, Inc. (Box 209)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous (Box 209)
    - D (Box 209)
    - Dantore Products (Box 209)
    - Dearborn-Massar (Box 210)
    - Donations and requests, 2 folders (Box 210)
    - Employees, Crowell and Smith (Box 210)
    - Employees, general file (Box 210)
    - Employees' withholding tax information (Box 211)
    - Ex-employee records (Box 211)
    - Exhibits (Box 211)
    - F (Box 211)
    - Federal Housing Administration (FHA) (Box 211)
    - Furniture Forum (Box 211)
    - G (Box 211)
    - Hart, Spencer & Boley, attorneys (Box 211)
    - House Beautiful (Box 211)
    - House and Garden (Box 211)
    - I (Box 211)
    - Inactive employees' withholding information (Box 211)
    - Insurance information (Box 211)
    - J, K, L (Box 212)
    - Ladies' Home Journal (Box 212)
    - Liturgical Arts (Box 212)
    - M (Box 212)
    - John Merrill, civil defense information (Box 212)
    - Miscellaneous publications, 3 folders (Box 212)
    - Miscellaneous small jobs (Box 213)
    - Moses report (Box 213)
    - Museum of Modern Art (Box 213)
    - N (Box 213)
    - National Architectural Accrediting Board (Box 213)
    - National Fire Protection Association (Box 213)
    - Newspaper clippings (Box 213)
    - Oregon Building Congress (Box 213)
    - Oregon Physicians' Service (Box 213)
    - Office operation and maintenance (Box 213)
    - P (Box 213)
    - Portland Art Museum, 3 folders (Box 214)
    - Portland Art Museum (Box 215)
    - Portland Art Museum, minutes and reports (Box 215)
    - Portland business study (Box 215)
    - Portland Executives Association (Box 215)
    - Portland Symphony Society (Box 215)
    - Post-war progress and building (Box 215)